Guide to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association records, circa 1800-2022 MS2027
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Images, Circa 1960-Circa 1998; MS2027 Series 1
  - Natural Landscape-Canal at unknown location, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 324)
  - Natural Landscape-Canal at unknown location, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 325)
  - Natural Landscape-Canal at unknown location, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 326)
  - Canal at unknown location, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 327)
  - Natural Landscape-Canal at unknown location, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 328)
  - Canal at unknown location, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 329)
  - Natural Landscape-Canal at unknown location, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 330)
  - Natural Landscape-Canal at unknown location, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 331)
  - Canal at unknown location, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 332)
  - Canal at unknown location, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 333)
  - Natural Landscape-Canal at unknown location, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 334)
  - Natural Landscape-Canal at unknown location, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 335)
  - Natural Landscape-Canal at unknown location, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 336)
  - Canal at unknown location, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 337)
  - Potomac River at Great Falls, 1989 January 03 (Box 25, Folder 338)
    Text on photograph: "Feeding the ducks & goose January 3, 1989 m 14.3 E. N. Holway"
  - Potomac River at Great Falls, 1989 May 12 (Box 25, Folder 339)
    Text on photograph: "Looking toward G Falls from Rocky Island Overlook 5/12/89 E. N. Holway"
  - Natural Landscape-Potomac River at Great Falls, 1984 November (Box 25, Folder 340)
    Text on photograph: "Rocks along Berm Road below Gr. Falls 11/84 E. N. Holway"
  - Potomac River at Great Falls, 1988 February (Box 25, Folder 341)
    Text on photograph: "Sunset @ Great Falls on a wintery day Feb 1988 canal just above Lock 20 E. N. Holway"
  - Potomac River at Great Falls, 1992 July (Box 25, Folder 342)
    Text on photograph: "Sunset over Rocky Island and Potomac 7/92 E. N. Holway"
  - Natural Landscape-Potomac River at Great Falls, 1993 October 17 (Box 25, Folder 343)
    Text on photograph: "Hollow sycamore tree 10/17/93 at Great Falls near Tavern E. N. Holway Nov 93"
  - Potomac River at Little Orleans, 1988 October 22 (Box 25, Folder 344)
    Text on photograph: "Fall on the Canal 10/22/88 Heritage Hike Lock 56 - Little Orleans E. N. Holway"
  - Potomac River at Olmsted Island, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 345)
    Text on photograph: "View upstream from a bridge Jul 92 1"
  - Potomac River at Olmsted Island, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 346)
    Text on photograph: "View from 2d bridge upstream Jul 92 1"
  - Potomac River at Olmsted Island, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 347)
    Text on the photograph: "View from one of the other bridges. Jul 92 1"
  - Potomac River at Olmsted Island, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 348)
    Text on photograph: "Looking upstream at River from overlook E. N. Holway Jul 92 1"
  - Potomac River at Olmsted Island, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 349)
    Text on photograph: "Moss covered rock Olmsted Id 11/14/93 E. N. Holway Dec 93"
  - Potomac River at Olmsted Island, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 350)
    Text on photograph: "Low water on stream under 1st overlook bridge 10/17/93 E. N. Holway Nov 93"
  - Potomac River at Olmsted Island, 1993 July 25 (Box 25, Folder 351)
    Text on photograph: "Low water - Potomac from G.F. overlook 7/25/93 E. N. Holway Aug 93"
  - Potomac River at Olmsted Island, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 352)
    Text on photograph: "Looking upstream from overlook E. N. Holway Jul 92 1"
  - Potomac River at Olmsted Island, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 353)
    Text on photograph: "Bent & rusty rods of old fence from early overlook at lower level are visible at left of picture - looking downstream from Olmsted Id overlook on MD shore."
  - Potomac River at Olmsted Island-Bridge opening ceremony, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 354)
    Text on photograph: "Sgt Hobbs addresses the gathering"
  - Potomac River at Olmsted Island-Bridge opening ceremony, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 355)
  - Potomac River at Olmsted Island-Bridge opening ceremony, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 356)
    Plaque on Rock at Overlook honoring F.L. Olmsted"
  - Potomac River at Olmsted Island-Bridge opening ceremony, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 357)
    Text on photograph: "Bill Hanna addresses the group"
  - Potomac River at Olmsted Island-Bridge opening ceremony, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 358)
    Text on photograph: "The bridge and boardwalk are disabled-friendly-ramp for wheelchairs."
  - Potomac River at Olmsted Island-Bridge opening ceremony, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 359)
    Text on photograph: "TV crew filming at overlook (You'll never again see this few people there!)
  - Potomac River at Olmsted Island-Bridge opening ceremony, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 360)
    Text on photograph: "Snipping the ribbon (Review 1st picture) before going across bridges"
  - Potomac River at Point of Rocks, undated (Box 25, Folder 361)
    Text on photographs: "Point of Rocks"
  - Potomac River at Violette's Lock, 1992 May (Box 25, Folder 362)
    Text on photograph: "Rapids Falls below Dam #2 May 1992 Violette's Lock area"
  - Potomac River at unknown location, undated (Box 25, Folder 363)
    Text on photograph: "Photography by Nicholas Dean 43 Martin Street Cambridge 38, Mass. Neg. No 88-7 20a 23 x 39 68% (Ductone Green & Black)
  - Potomac River at unknown location, undated (Box 25, Folder 364)
  - Potomac River at Brunswick, Circa 1967 (Box 25, Folder 365)
    Text on photograph: "Potomac R. @ Brunswick Area"
  - Annual meeting at Sheperdstown, 1992 March 16 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Text on photograph: "Annual Meeting - Shepherdstown John Fondorsmith, John Chandler, Carl Linden Photo by Ralph Donnolly"
  - Annual meeting at Sheperdstown, 1993 March 06 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Text on photograph: "Annual Meeting - Sheperdstown Adole Donnolly, Joan Paull Photo by Donnolly"
  - Annual meeting at Shepherdstown, 1993 March 06 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Text on photograph: "Annual Meeting - Shepherdstown Karen Clay, John Woodward, Emmie Woordward Photo by Ralph Donnolly"
  - Annual meeting at Shepherdstwon, 1993 March 06 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Text on photograph: "Annual Meeting - Shepherdstown Dave Johnson, Karen Gray, Adole Donnolly Photo by Ralph Donnolly"
  - Annual meeting at Shepherdstown, 1993 March 06 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    Text on photograph: "Annual Meeting - Shepherdstown Tom Hobbs, Carl Linden, Hal Larsen Photo by Ralph Donnolly"
  - Annual meeting at Shepherdstown, 1993 March 06 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    Text on photograph: "Annual Meeting: Shepherdstown John Fondorsmith, John Chandler Photo by Ralph Donnolly"
  - Annual meeting at Shepherdstwon, 1993 March 06 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Text on photograph: "Annual Meeting - Shepherdstown Hal Larsen, Tom Hobbs Photo by Ralph Donnolly"
  - Annual meeting at Shepherdstown, 1993 March 06 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Annual meeting at Shepherdstown, 1993 March 06 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    Text on photograph: "Annual Meeting - Shepherdstown Nancy Long, Adam Fostor, Tom Hobbs, Dave Johnson Photo by Ralph Donnolly"
  - Annual meeting at Shepherdstown, 1993 March 06 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    Text on photograph: "Shepherdstown, WVA Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Meet left: Minny Pohlmann, Virginia Long Right: Dave Johnson, John Chandler, Bill Evans, Bob Perry"
  - Annual meeting at Shepherdstown, 1993 March 06 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    Text on photograph: "Marlow Madisoy, Ann Wright, Keith Kridenoff, Chis Ayriss, Bill Speck, Adam Fostor"
  - Annual meeting at Shepherdstown, 1993 March 06 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    Text on photograph: "Shepherdstown WVA Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Meet John Seabury Thomson, Hal Larsen, Jane Larsen, Paul Rosa, Waine Corniglia"
  - Board meeting at Williamsport, 1993 June 27 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    Text on photograph: "The rest of the Board of Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Assn mtg Williampsort 6/27/93"
    Text with photograph: "V - Photo Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Board Meeting, Williamsport, Jun 27, 1993 L-R: David Johnson, Hal Larsen, Ralph Donnelly, John Fondersmith, Orrin Long, Keith Kuivendoff, Charles Ayers, Nancy Long, Carl Linden, Linda Perry, Lyman Stucker, Several, By Ellen Holway"
  - Board meeting at Williamsport, 1993 June 27 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    Text on photograph: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Assn Bd Mtg 6/27/93"
    Text with photograph: "V - Photo - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Board Meeting, Williamsport, Jun 27, 1993 L to R: Kenneth Rollins, Carl Linden, Linda Perry, david Johnson, William Evans, Ralph donnelly, John Fondersmith, Orrin Long, Several, By Ellen Holway"
  - Board meeting at Williamsport, 1994 June 26 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    Text on photograph: "Chesapeake & Ohio Caaal [sic] Association board meeting, June 26, 1994, Williamsport, MD library. L to P: Nax Ellen Holway, Ken Rollins, Nancy Long, Carl Linden Photo by Hal Larsen"
  - Board meeting at Williamsport, 1994 June 26 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    Text on photograph: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Assn Board meeting, June 26, 1994, Williampsort, MD. L to R: Ken Rollins, elizabeth Scott, Nancy Long, Carl Linden Photo by Hal Larsen"
  - Board meeting at Williamsport, 1994 June 26 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    Text on photograph: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Assn board meeting, June 26, 1994, Williamsport, MS, library. Clockwise (faces visible) from L to R: Ken Rollins, Charley Ayers, Keith Kridenoff, Gary Petrichick, Lyman Stucker, William Bauman, Tom Perry, Tom Conlon, Elizabeth Scott, Nancy Long. Photo by Hal Larsen"
  - Board meeting at Williamsport, 1994 June 26 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    Text on photograph: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Board meeting, June 26, 1994 Williamsport, MD Library Clockwise (faces visible) from L to R: Tom Perry, John Fondersmith, Ellen Holway, Tom Conlon, Nancy Long, Jane Larsen Carl Linden, Charley Ayers, Lyman Stucker"
  - 2 Men-Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Natural Landscapes, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Railroad Train, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Car accident, Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Natural Landscapes, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Member-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Member-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Member-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Natural Landscape, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Aqueduct, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Man on horse, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Man with Confederate Flag on horse, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Man with Confederate flag on horse, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Man with Confederate flag on horse at a distance, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Man with Confederate flag on horse at a distance, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Man with Confederate flag on horse, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Women and children with sign, Circa 1959 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-Colin Ritter, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association members with Lady Bird Johnson, Circa 1969 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    Text on photograph: "Lady Bird Johnson & others,"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Member-Raymond Riley, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    Text on photograph: "Raymond Riley Summer 86 m 22.82"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Member-Richard Stanton, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    Text on photograph: "What does the Supt do on his days off? He picks up the cans on HIS levels (levels 68 and 69). These are assigned to Bruce Wood but I took them over.. he's never around"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Member-Richard Stanton, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - People carryin canoe, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Canoeing, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    Text on photograph: "June 2, the foltilla [sic] arriving at Harpers Ferry, up the Shenandoah."
  - Canoe at Lockhouse 68, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 58)
    Text on photograph: "A lunch stop at Lockhouse 68... Grant and I had a drink here with ISAAC LONG on the porch many years ago... Ike luved [sic] here."
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Member-Edie Roundbush, 1990 July 25 (Box 26, Folder 59)
    Text on photograph: "Edie Roundbush playing dulcimer during Canal presentation at Claggett Ctr 7/25/90"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-Ellen Holway & Tom Perry, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - President of Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association David Johnson at Lock 14 for membership committee meeting, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - President of Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association David Johnson at Lock 14 for membership committee meeting, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 62)
    Text on photograph: "Cardorock - Membership Committee Hike Photo by Orrin Long"
  - President of Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association David Johnson at Lock 14 for membership committee meeting, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - President of Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association David Johnson at Lock 14 for membership committee meeting, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - President of Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association David Johnson at Lock 14 for membership committee meeting, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - President of Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association David Johnson at Lock 14 for membership committee meeting, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 66)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Member-John Frye, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 67)
    Text on photograph: "John Frye explaining the Conococheague Aqueduct to a shivering audience."
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Member-Frank Galvin, 1994 November 06 (Box 26, Folder 68)
    Text on photograph: "Lil & Frank Galvin Freat Falls Nov. 6, 1994"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Member-David Johnson, 1994 May 30 (Box 26, Folder 69)
    Text on photograph: "David Johsnon, at Lock 44, Williamsport, May 30, 1994"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Member-David Johnson, 1994 March 05 (Box 26, Folder 70)
    Text on photograph: "pg 5a 5 March 94"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Member-Lillian Langdon, 1994 May (Box 26, Folder 71)
    Text on photograph: "Lillian C. Langdon (May, 1994) looking at her birthplace, near the old aqueduct bridge on the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal near Georgetown."
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Member-Lillian Langdon, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 72)
    Text on photograph: "Lillian C. Langdon with piecework, Paw-Paw Tunnel & by Canal Picture painted by her daughter in law"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Member-Harold Larsen, 1994 March 05 (Box 26, Folder 73)
    Text on photograph: "5 March 94 pg 5-b"
  - Various canal walkers, undated (Box 26, Folder 74)
  - Various canal walkers, undated (Box 26, Folder 75)
  - Natural Landscape and canal walkers, undated (Box 26, Folder 76)
  - Canal, undated (Box 26, Folder 77)
  - Canal walkers, undated (Box 26, Folder 78)
  - Canal walkers, undated (Box 26, Folder 79)
  - Various canal walkers, undated (Box 26, Folder 80)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, undated (Box 26, Folder 81)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, undated (Box 26, Folder 82)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, undated (Box 26, Folder 83)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, undated (Box 26, Folder 84)
  - Construction workers, undated (Box 26, Folder 85)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association Members-unknown, undated (Box 26, Folder 86)
  - Sign for the the Western Maryland Sportsman's Club, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 87)
    Sign for the the Western Maryland Sportsman's Club.
  - Merry-go-round horses, undated (Box 26, Folder 88)
  - Hike Four Locks to Mile post 117, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 89)
  - Canoe trip, 1993 July (Box 26, Folder 90)
  - Canoe Trip, 1993 July (Box 26, Folder 91)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association clothes patch, undated (Box 26, Folder 92)
  - Lithograph, "Lock 15 of Chesapeake & Ohio Canal", by Barbara Yeaman, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 93)
    Text on lithograph: "106/200 Lock 15 Chesapeake & Ohio Canal B. Yeaman '76 "man's true destiny is... with all the other living things in the universe." WM. O. Douglas"
    Limited printing #106 of 200
  - Plant, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 94)
  - Natural Landscape, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 95)
  - Natural Landscape, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 96)
    Stamped on the back "APR1983"
  - Natural Landscape, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 97)
  - House, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 98)
  - House, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 99)
  - House, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 100)
    Stamped on the back "APR 1984"
  - Bridge, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 101)
  - Bridge, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 102)
  - Aqueduct, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 103)
  - Natural Landscape, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 104)
  - Structure, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 105)
  - Aqueduct, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 106)
  - Natural Landscape, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 107)
  - Natural Landscape, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 108)
  - Men sitting, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 109)
  - People cooking, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 110)
    Stamped on back "APR 1984"
  - People eating, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 111)
  - Man-name unknown, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 112)
    Stamped on the back "APR 1983"
  - Men, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 113)
  - Men, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 114)
    Stamped on back "SEP 1983"
  - People, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 115)
  - Women sitting, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 116)
    Stamped on the back "SEP 1983"
  - People, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 117)
  - People, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 118)
  - People, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 119)
  - People, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 120)
  - Men, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 121)
  - Men, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 122)
  - Men, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 123)
  - People, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 124)
  - People, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 125)
  - Plaque, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 126)
  - Natural Landscape, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 127)
  - Campers and canoes, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 128)
  - Natural Landscape, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 129)
  - House, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 130)
  - People cleaning, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 131)
  - Interior of house, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 132)
  - House, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 133)
  - Man carrying mailbox, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 134)
  - House, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 135)
  - House, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 136)
  - Hikers, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 137)
  - Hikers, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 138)
  - Hikers, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 139)
  - Hikers, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 140)
  - Hikers, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 141)
  - Tanks with cartoon faces painted on them, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 142)
    Tanks with cartoon faces painted on them in the rear of the house.
  - People cleaning, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 143)
    Stamped on the back MAY 88.
  - People cleaning, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 144)
    Stamped on the back "MAY 1988"
  - People, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 145)
    Stamped on the back "MAY 88"
  - Man in snow covered landscape, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 146)
    Text on photograph: "Dave Johnson"
  - People, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 147)
    Text on photograph: "Jim Lawrence, Sue Anne Sullivan, Al Stanley & Jane Larsen"
  - People, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 148)
    Text on photograph: "Jim Lawrence, Karen Gray & Lou Odom I can't identify the other 4."
  - Railroads Track, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 149)
    Stamped on photograph "MAY 88"
  - Pillar, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 150)
    Stamped on photograph: "MAY 88"
  - People boarding bus, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 151)
  - People, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 152)
    Stamp on photograph: "MAR 88"
  - Women, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 153)
  - People drinking, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 154)
  - Natural landscape, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 155)
    Stamp on photograph: "SEP 1984"
  - Natural landscape, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 156)
  - Women taking a break from hike, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 157)
  - People sitting, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 158)
  - Woman lieing on grass, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 159)
  - Natural landscape, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 160)
  - Natural landscape, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 161)
  - Natural landscape, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 162)
  - Natural landscape, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 163)
  - Natural landscape, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 164)
  - People on bridge, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 165)
  - People hiking with dog, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 166)
    Text on photograph: "Chesapeake & Ohio Hike 4-26-86 Four Locks to Licking Creek - End of hike"
  - People hiking, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 167)
    Text on photograph: "Western Md. Railway Trestle Chesapeake & Ohio Hike 4-26-86 Four Locks to Licking Creek"
  - Woman with bicycle, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 168)
    Text on photograph: "3/26 Big Pool/Chesapeake & Ohio hike Four Locks to Licking Creek"
  - People resting from hike, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 169)
    Text on photograph: "Chesapeake & Ohio hike Hancock to Dam 6 10-25-86"
  - Ferry Hill Plantation, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 170)
  - People waiting to board a bus at Ferry Hill Plantation, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 171)
    Text on photograph: "Justice Douglas Reunion Hike 4/30/88 (Dargan's Bend-Shepherdstown) Waiting to board the bus at Ferry Hill"
  - Lunch at mountain lock, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 172)
  - Boarding the bus at Ferry Hill, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 173)
    Text on photograph: "Justice Douglas Reunion Hike 4/30/88 (Dargan's Bend-Shepherdstown) Boarding the bus at Ferry Hill"
  - Happy hour at Tom Hahn's house, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 174)
    Text on photograph: "Justice Douglas Reunion Hike 4/30/88 (Dargan's Bend-Shepherdstown) Happy hour at Tom Hahn's house, Shepherdstown, W.Va.--Cashier & friend"
  - Happy hour at Tom Hahn's house, Circa 1988 (Box 26, Folder 175)
    Text on photograph: "Justice Douglas Reunion Hike 4/30/88 (Dargan's Bend-Shepherdstown) Happy Hour at Tom Hahn's house, Shepherdstown, W. Va."
  - Christmas at Great Falls Tavern, Circa 1985 (Box 26, Folder 176)
    Text with photograph: "Christmas at Great Falls Tavern mile 14"
  - Ducks on ice, Circa 1985 (Box 26, Folder 177)
    Text with photograph: "Ducks on ice mile 14"
  - Spring along the towpath at Widewater, Circa 1985 (Box 26, Folder 178)
    Text with photograph: "Spring along the Towpath at Widewater mile 12"